ufv.ca 2009-12-28

# Privacy Statement

Your privacy at UFV

UFV and protection of personal information  
As a public body, UFV complies with the following privacy provisions of BC's Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act (RSBC 1996 ch. 165):

  * Personal information is collected directly from the individual about whom it relates 
  * Personal information is secured from unauthorized access 
  * Personal information is collected, used, and disclosed for purposes consistent with UFV's program and service offerings 
  * Individuals have the right of access to and a right to request correction of their own personal information 
  * Personal information is retained for the time period to fulfill the purposes for which it was collected 
  * Individuals will be notified about the purposes for which information is collected, and when information is collected for optional use, individuals will consent to the information collection.

For more information about UFV's privacy procedures, you may contact:

Marketing and Communications  
University of the Fraser Valley  
33844 King Rd  
Abbotsford, BC   
Canada V2S 7M8  
Tel: 604-504-7441

Notification regarding UFV's web site and personal information  
As a visitor to UFV's web site, UFV's web servers automatically collect information that is essential to operating and maintaining the site's security. The information collected includes:

Browser type   
Internet service provider (ISP) name   
IP address  
The extent of personal information collected by UFV's web servers depends on the standards followed by your ISP. You may wish to contact your provider to determine the policies and practices in this regard.

UFV's web site contains links to third-party sites, and UFV is not responsible for the privacy provisions of those other web sites.

Some portions of the UFV web site may distribute small pieces of information (called "cookies") to web browsers to assist you when you return to specific areas on the site. If you have concerns about cookies, you can change your web browser settings not to accept this information, or display warning messages.

When you voluntarily send electronic mail to UFV or complete an electronic form that includes identifying information about you, UFV will keep a record of this information so that we can respond to you.
